EPISODE 5
HAPPY MOMENT
Hmm.
Ka-ze-haya!
Where do you think you're going, huh?
- I've already got your song loaded up.
- Sorry, but I--
But nothing.
You're not sneaking out of your own party!
- Hey, Kazehaya.
- Huh?
What time did you say
we had this room till?
- Nine.
- Oh, hey, there you are. For you.
Let's get an extension.
- Or an after-party.
- Yo, Kazehaya. Over here. Look.
Sorry. Party's all yours from here on out.
Do what you want.
What the heck, dude.
- Where's he going?
- Kazehaya?
Huh?
Kazehaya.
Sorry.
- I'm okay now.
- Ah.
- Ha-ha! Hey, don't you worry, kid.
- Pin?!
Why are you here?
- Now, now. Don't sweat the details.
- Thank you for the tissue.
Just a little housekeeping
after a quarrel, that's all.
What quarrel?
Hey, Kuronuma.
- You should probably head back first.
- Huh?
Sure.
Been meanin' to ask ya.
How long have you two been goin' out?
That came outta nowhere!
I dunno, six months?
Six months, you say?
Impressive, young man.
Huh! Very impressive!
Wha-- what do you mean?
For six whole months, you've resisted
the temptations of the flesh.
Amazing!
A man of my experience
can tell just by looking.
Wha-- Tell what?
Listen. The path
which you have chosen is correct.
Excellent job.
Don't you ever change, kid.
Uh-- uh-- uh-- Wha-- Ne-- never?
Seriously, though.
You know what the right thing to do is,
don't you? And you're trying your best?
Yeah. I am trying, but I don't know
if it's actually the right thing.
- Well, that's too bad 'cause neither do I!
- What?
All right! I think it's about that time!
Get ready, kids,
I'm about to give you the boot!
It's that late?
What do we do? Where's Kazehaya?
He's not the only one missing.
Closing time, kiddos!
All right, I'm putting a bow
on this shindig!
Now, get your butts outta here,
it's past your bedtime!
Oh hush!
And don't you even
think about an after-party.
You kids better head
straight on home. No detours.
Come on, it's Christmas!
Can't you turn a blind eye?
Sorry, pal. My personal rule is
I only turn one blind eye a day.
And I've already met my quota.
Go on, beat it! Scram.
Hey, is that Ayane's bag?
Y-- yeah.
Master.
Ayane.
Sawako.
Kento... is gonna walk me home.
Looks like that's that.
- Hey!
- Huh?
- Is the party breaking up already?
- Chizu. Here. Your bag.
Oh, thanks. Sorry to trouble you.
Huh? Where's Yano-chin?
Um, she just left.
What?! Just like that?
Hey, she's not angry at me
for suddenly disappearing, is she?
- Oh no, she's not mad at all.
- Chizuru.
Ready to go?
Uh, yeah. Coming.
Sawa.
Hey, uh, let's find time to talk later.
Mm!
I'll give her the present on the way home.
I have no idea
if it's the right thing or not.
I just...
Whenever I get too close, I lose control.
If Kuronuma were within my reach
and I held out my hand... and touched her,
I know for a fact I'd pull her in
and hold her as tight as I could.
I would kiss her.
All the distance
between us would fade away.
But that would be wrong.
What I really want is to cherish her.
Forever.
And that means,
keeping a respectful distance.
You've been holdin' back, right?
You ready?
Mm... mmm.
Oh, it's those two.
Wait, are they still goin' out?
Man, I thought for sure
they had broken up.
They came to the party though.
Oh right.
You're not in our class, are you?
Let's go.
Yeah.
Man, I thought for sure
they had broken up.
Are we still... going out?
Can you blame me?
Kazehaya never tells me a thing.
Tomorrow is the start
of winter vacation... Kazehaya.
Maybe... this is what it's come to.
Maybe... one day...
we're both going to look up and realize
that we aren't a couple any longer.
I've always dreaded
our time as a couple ending abruptly.
But, what if we're already...
What if
we're not...
So, yeah, things may be
a little weird between you at the moment.
But, if you close your eyes
and wait for five seconds,
well, I bet anything
things'll get sorted out.
Uh...
Wha--
What's the matter, Kuronuma?
That's the last time...
I roll the dice.
You lied... to me.
Kazehaya, you lied. You're a liar!
You said you wouldn't know
what to do if I did that again. You liar.
You say nothing's bothering you,
but I know that's not true.
All I wanted for us today...
...was to be able to spend time together.
Last year, I desperately wanted us
to have this time.
I understand that you've been
really busy with your work...
I get it, I do.
The present I wanted him
to accept from me...
I can't give it,
even though we're together now.
But......I feel lonelier
than when I was by myself.
Is being with me
what's been bothering you?
Did you start having second thoughts?
Do you...
not like me anymore?
You don't like me as I am anymore?
Of course he doesn't. Why would he?
I like you.
I like you!
Kazehaya.
Kazehaya!
Finally.
You're finally... looking at me.
Yeah, 'cause I really love you.
Yeah.
This is what really mattered.
I wanna talk. But properly.
It might take a while though.
I'd like that too.
Oh, yes, hi, Mom.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I, uh... I might be out a while.
Right. Yes. He's with me.
Huh? Dad?
Uh.
No, wait, Dad. Hang on. Just this once!
After that, I'll... I'll do better.
I swear, I'll double down
on my chores and studies.
Kuronuma.
Is it okay if I talk to him a sec?
Uh, hello? This is Kazehaya. I, uh...
Just one hour.
That's all I'm asking for, sir.
Yes.
I'll make sure
she gets home safe. Yes, sir.
Yes.
Right.
I will. Thank you, sir.
Goodbye.
Forty-five minutes, he said.
I tried, but that's all
he was willing to give me.
You see, Sawako, your dad understands.
He says that you've been brave
for long enough.
Huh?
Please, enjoy.
Last Christmas...
you couldn't make it, right?
I swore that I'd never
let you feel sad or alone.
I told myself I'd never let that happen.
That's when he...
But...
...in spite of that,
I'm the one who made you sad.
Sorry.
I kept thinking in circles,
and it made you anxious.
I'm sorry for that.
It wasn't my intention at all.
When I went over to your house
and met both your mother and father,
I, uh, I wanted to show how serious I was.
Show how I cherish you.
At least... that's what I wanted.
I'll treasure you
from now till the end of time.
My intentions for us are serious.
And as for Christmas,
after what happened last year,
I thought a group activity
would have made you happy.
Even so... there's another problem.
I don't have confidence.
Like that time on our class trip.
I lost my cool, immediately.
I don't know if you can
even imagine how much I like you.
It's true.
My imagination could never
fill in the blanks.
From the very first day,
you weren't like anyone I'd ever met.
I mean it.
Ever since that time,
you've always been right here.
My heart has never been without you.
Always?
From the first day we met?
This whole time?
Thank you so much.
It's because I'm self-centered.
Honestly, it doesn't matter
what anyone else says or thinks,
there's always a part of me
that just doesn't care.
I think it's really rare
to find people you can truly open up to.
I guess
that's why I have a tendency
to keep people at arm's length.
For a while,
it was just instinct, I think.
But, I...
I just can't stay away from you,
no matter what.
I care about everything you say and think.
It's embarrassing, but...
I really wanted to play it cool.
Until I met you... I had no idea
that I was this kind of person.
This is a Kazehaya I have never known.
When I first met you...
If you happen to be looking for
Kitahoro High and you're lost,
it's that way.
Has something been... bothering you?
I can't.
If I get too close, I'll...
Is that cool?
If I borrow Sadako to talk alone.
Ya dumb jerk.
If that's how you're gonna put it,
of course I'd wanna say no.
I...
The thing about me is I'm a petty guy.
So damn petty.
- That's amazing!
- Huh?
Thanks, Sadako.
You made it so easy to understand.
Thank you, Sadako!
I wanna see her smile.
When I'm happy for her, it's real.
But...
I want her for myself.
I know... that's not something I can have.
If I just took what I wanted,
then all their hard work
would have been for nothing.
My life would be completely different
without you in it, Kazehaya.
That's funny.
I'm the one who should be saying that.
- Each time we encounter each other...
- Hm?
...I'm the one...
...who falls even deeper.
The thing is... I, uh...
I don't know
if the "me" that you see even exists.
The version of Kazehaya
that I see is...
...so refreshing, right down to your name.
Truth is, I have zero intention
of ever giving you up.
I like you.
But in spite of that,
or maybe because of it...
...I don't know
if I could cherish you how you deserve.
But even so,
I don't ever wanna let you go.
Even if it means... I might end up
becoming your greatest source of pain.
Kazehaya.
Don't you see it?
You deserve to be
with somebody who's worthy of you.
I don't know
if that's a scary, selfish guy like me.
Kazehaya...
I know you could do so much better.
Do you honestly not see it?
He says he's self-centered.
He doesn't know
how happy his genuine smile makes me.
How happy it makes all those around him.
He says he's scary.
But right now, he doesn't have any idea
how glad I am to hear him say those words.
The only one who could hurt me
so deeply... is you.
And I'm fully aware of that.
Because only you can reach this deep
into my heart.
I think it's okay if things get awkward
or if we have a fight.
'Cause even when things
are hard or there's conflict...
I'll still want to be with you.
I don't care if it's not right.
If always chasing after someone
without ever reaching them
is unrequited love...
then, in truth, the two of us
should be able to stand face-to-face
and look each other in the eye.
If we can stand together
and face these challenges side-by-side,
then our love will flourish.
Sorry. Just this time.
- Hey, Kazehaya?
- Huh?
Y'know how
you keep insisting you're different
from whatever version
of you I'm perceiving?
Well...
I'm pretty sure I'm not wrong about this.
You see, I can just tell.
Every single thing
you do and say feels genuine to me.
It's okay if I'm not right.
Even if none of it is right, all of it is.
Here's the thing about Shota.
He's narrow-minded and stubborn.
If he's made up his mind, it's over.
The kid's head
is harder than a brick wall.
Deep down, he's really tough on himself.
And on others.
Well, not that that's a bad thing.
If only he'd learn
how to vent and let it all out!
See? I happen to be a master of the art.
If you cannot contend
with the weaknesses in yourself,
then how could you do so
with the weaknesses in others?
Hey! Did you hear a word I just said?!
- And why aren't you writing this down!
- Oh. My. Gosh!
How am I supposed to enjoy my ramen
when you won't shut up?!
Watch it!
- You should be grateful for my wisdom.
- What?
Really, Pin?
You enjoy ambushing students
with lectures at Christmastime, huh?
Damn right!
Now, let me hear you kids say thank you!
You two were wandering aimlessly.
Right up until I blessed you
with my great knowledge.
Merry Christmas!
Right, then.
You two should
probably help Shota open up.
Yeah, right!
If he opens up to anyone, it'll be Sawa!
Argh! Why is everything so hard!
Jeez, what's her problem?
Christmas spirit burning too hot? Ha!
I wonder if, somewhere in me,
those strong feelings
of longing are still there.
I always believed that
once two people became intimate,
they'd never have to worry
about the distance between them again.
Guess I was wrong.
The more you like them,
the more you worry.
About all the ways
they keep their distance.
About every gesture and every
little change in their expression.
And because you like them,
every last little detail
doesn't matter anymore.
Please.
Let us always have faith
in our feelings for each other.
You're not the only one
learning about yourself.
The truth is, I am too.
Huh?
Sometimes,
I get jealous of the boys.
It's true, I do.
I can get really possessive.
Like, really possessive.
Kazehaya... I can walk the rest of the way.
What? But we're almost there?
I'm sorry I yelled and called you a liar!
Why apologize? I am a liar.
I'm home!
Oh, Sawako. You're back.
My, you're home
sooner than expected.
What are you talking about?
She only had five minutes left, you know?
I didn't think she'd care
about the time limit.
Wha-- Huh?
Did Kazehaya walk you home?
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry I stayed out late.
No, everything's fine!
You kept your promise, after all.
Besides, it's the holidays. It's special.
You look freezing.
Come on, hop into the bath
before you catch a cold.
'Kay.
The last secret... of my 16th year.
Kazehaya, you lied. You're a liar!
Is being with me
what's been bothering you?
You don't like me as I am anymore?
Only you could hurt me.
I'm sorry I yelled and called you a liar!
I'll never get to sleep.
INCOMING CALL
Hmm?
Who's calling at this hour?
Yes? Uh, hello?
Kazehaya! What's good?
CLICK
Hung up without thinking.
Wha-- Who's this?
Um, hello?
That hurt my feelings, you know?
Hanging up like that.
It's your old buddy Kent--
Hello?
- Kazehaya!
- Sorry.
- That was so mean!
- I said I'm sorry.
So, I guess you can do whatever you want,
no matter how
it might affect someone else.
This coming from the guy
who's calling me at 2:30 in the morning?
Still, for some reason,
connecting with the guy
feels strangely easy.
So, what's up?
Oh, you know,
just doing my duty and reporting in.
Like a good friend would!
What are you talking about?
Ooh, want the details?
You're so hopeless, Kazehaya.
Will you stop? Let's hear it.
Well, here goes...
As of this moment,
I'm officially going out with Ayane!
Huh?
Uh...
Oh!
Hold on.
Did you hear something from Sadako?
Uh, no, she didn't tell me anything.
I see.
Gotcha.
I'm happy for you.
To be honest,
I wasn't as smooth as I wanted to be.
I got her a bouquet of roses,
but then Joe went
and stepped on it.
Did you say a bouquet of roses?!
Totally seems like her thing, right?
The reddest I could find.
I was a nervous wreck.
By the way, I ran into Mogi-cchi today.
Uh-huh.
- And I kinda decked him in the schnoz.
- Uh-huh.
Wait a sec, you're not surprised?
Why'd you hit him?
Oh, I'm not one to punch and tell!
Goodbye.
Well, long story short,
he said some things about Ayane
that I just couldn't let slide...
so I didn't.
Mmm.
Thinking back on it, it was probably
jealousy that drove me to do it.
I'm curious.
- You think I made a difference?
- Mm-hmm.
So, the two of you are a couple now,
aren't you?
You're gonna show her a good time
and treat her like a princess, right?
Mmm.
How about you?
Me? I, uh...
What am I saying?
- I'm not worried about you two at all.
- What?!
Remember what I said
the last time you called me for advice?
You and sweet Sadako
have absolutely nothing to worry about.
When did I ask him for advice?
But, let's get back to Ayane.
Uh, sure?
She's so adorable and so kind too.
There's a million reasons to love her.
I'm tellin' ya, nobody knows the real her.
There are guys out there who would
write off a girl so sweet and gorgeous
and awesome and cool, can you believe it?!
What's wrong with people these days?
I mean, I guess there's no helping
terrible taste, but still,
it totally boggles my mind.
Honestly, I could go on about
the things to love about her.
I could start right now and keep going
for hours, maybe even days.
Even after that,
I could come up with new stuff.
- Hey, you there, buddy?
- Huh?! Yeah. Yep.
I can say it. At last.
I know what love is!
Yi... yippee.
Until last year, I always woke up
to a present next to my pillow.
Here's a sign
that it wasn't all just a dream.
Good morning!
- There you are. Good morning, dear.
- Hey, kiddo.
Sawako!
Did you think your father and I had
forgotten about your Christmas present?
Oh, thank you!
The scarf was personally chosen
by yours truly.
What an incredible coincidence
because I got you a scarf too!
- You did what?!
- Here.
- We're... in... sync!
I'm so happy for you, honey.
And thank you for the shawl. I love it.
Oh, it pains me to have to leave,
but work's calling.
I must get going.
Oh, let's have our party
the moment I get home, okay?
Right then, ladies. I'm off!
See you tonight.
Come on, hun.
You should go finish your breakfast.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
A text message?
Coming!
- We're here!
Make yourself at home.
Welcome.
Thanks for having us!
We texted you pretty last-minute.
You sure us dropping by
isn't too much trouble?
No, not at all. I'm glad.
We didn't really get to talk much
yesterday, but now's our chance.
You're right! Holy crap,
I've got so much to tell you!
Argh! Where do I begin?!
Try sitting down first?
I have news too.
I was thinking, we could take some time
to catch each other up on our lives.
Uh, why is everybody so quiet?
Someone say something or I'll explode!
Um, I mean,
you seemed the most eager to share,
so we were just waiting
for you to say something.
Oh wow. That's a lotta sweat.
Hey! Sawa!
I thought you had news to report?
The floor is yours! Go!
So, yesterday,
I cried and told him
I was having some doubts.
But... we're all better now.
You had doubts?
Wait! This is massive!
I see. You talked after the party, huh?
Mm-hmm. It was past my curfew.
But, I'm glad we stayed out.
Because I... I think,
thanks to our conversation,
us being together
finally feels real to me.
- Good for you.
But what does she mean by doubts?!
I just don't get it!
Your relationship with Kazehaya's always
been clear skies and smooth talking!
"Smooth sailing," not talking.
But why did you cry?
Why'd you have doubts?!
Wait, so there is something?
Come to think of it, it totally seems
like something is bothering Kazehaya.
Now... it... all makes sense!
I really am sorry, Chizu!
Wait! Did Kazehaya cheat on you
even though you're way out of his league?
- That good-for-nothing little--
- Cheat on me? There's no way!
He would never do that to me!
Not in a million years!
That's her first thought?
That's how badly
communication broke down?
Yano-chin, did you know this?
Yeah, I was aware, but timing-wise,
it was a bit tricky.
You see, this was right after
you ran off to buy Ryu's present.
That's when she told me about it.
- So how about you, Chizu?
- Huh?
I know something happened
between you and Ryu.
Since you never came back to the party.
I mean, yeah,
something did happen, but, uh...
Hey, I don't think I like the way
you guys are staring at me. Um...
Gah!
I need time to prepare myself emotionally!
Sure.
In that case,
I suppose I'll just go first.
Kento and I are now dating.
Ayane!
After a while, it starts to feel
like every guy'll be the same.
That I'll never have anything serious.
I can't help it. That's just how I feel.
Have you ever...
stopped to consider
how that behavior
might have made her feel?!
I'll be the one to comfort her.
Master...
you reached her!
I'm so happy for you!
Huh? Wait, you said Kento?!
That doofus
is your boyfriend?!
Yes, I'm referring to that Kento.
But why that idiot?!
Oh right.
I forgot she doesn't know
about any of this yet.
Ah, I see. This is all just a dream!
Sorry, it's all real.
That really hurts.
Now that I think about it,
back at the start of second year,
there was a time
you couldn't shut up about Kento!
Were you two already a thing then?
Not at all.
That was something else.
Wait, doesn't this surprise you?
Have I been that clueless
this entire time?
Well, yeah, you were. So clueless.
At the start
of the Christmas party yesterday,
you two weren't a couple yet, right?
What the heck happened?
Uh, well, you see...
Truth is, it didn't exactly
come out of nowhere.
During free activities time
on our class trip,
Kento and I bumped into each other
after I had just broken up with Mogi.
I kind of started crying.
Not because I was sad over the breakup.
I think I might've
accidentally let my guard down a little.
But even so,
I don't think it was a mistake.
Whenever he's around, I start to relax.
Honestly, he's a really sweet guy.
Still, I can't help but wonder
if I made the right call.
Huh? Did you just
suddenly realize he sucks?
What?! No!
I genuinely think he's a great guy.
In fact, he's nothing like any of the
other guys I've gone out with so far.
I guess that's why
I was so touched.
Sawako, if you asked me right now
if I liked Kento
the same way you like Kazehaya,
I honestly couldn't tell you.
But this is the first time
anyone's been so passionate about me
and so determined to stand up for me.
It made me ridiculously happy.
So, no, I don't think he sucks at all.
The thing is,
I don't have that much faith in myself.
So the issue isn't Kento. It's me.
That's why I keep wondering
if this was the right choice.
- Course everything's fine!
- You did another one-eighty.
Okay, look, I can't say I really get it.
If I'm being honest, I can't name
a single thing I like about the guy.
But if his is the shoulder
you wanna cry on,
then fine, I'll share you.
And when that's over with,
I'll still be here! 'Kay?
Way to jinx it!
Still, thanks, I guess.
Well?
Eh?
- Well?
- Eh?
- Mm-hmm?
Eh?
It's your turn now. Go ahead.
You seriously expect me
to follow those two stories?
C'mon, how am I supposed to do that?
You're not getting off the hook.
We want every detail.
I should have gone first.
Anyway...
this is one of those, uh, pickled flowers.
"Pickled flower"?
Uh, yeah! They do that thing
to make it last longer.
Do you mean a preserved flower?
Oh! Uh, yeah, that.
Wow, look at that.
Yeah, a lovely pink rose!
Isn't it... so very pink?
Very, very pink!
Huh?
Does it remind you of me?
Tell me. Does it?
- Do you think of me when you see it?
- Mmmmm!
It's so you! It's very you!
Chizu, your pupils are
very dilated right now.
So anyway, what did you do
after he gave you this?
Huh? What do you mean, what did I do?
Do I have to spell it out?
This is a pink rose!
- A pi-- pickled--
- Preserved!
So, did you just accept it
and leave it at that,
or did something else happen?
Huh?! Well, I gave him a present!
I, uh, stole it back from Joe.
But yeah, I, uh...
- I sorta feel bad for the guy.
- No need to worry.
Ayane didn't miss a beat
and gave Joe her rock salt.
Whoa! Thank you, Yano-chin!
Let's not get sidetracked!
The two of you suddenly disappeared
for a suspiciously long
stretch of time during the party.
I wanna know what happened. Now!
We just talked about normal stuff,
like what we'd had
for dinner last night, and...
After you got this?
...and TV shows...
...and ramen...
Really? After you got this pink rose?!
You... you did
naughty adult things!
That has to be it!
We talked about when we were kids.
About Toru.
And about his late mother.
But there's just never enough time.
We share so many memories.
It's been so long since we got
to sit down and talk like that.
Oh yeah. He mentioned Toru's
gonna be home for New Year's.
- Is he really? You gonna see him?
- Yeah, I'd like that.
See him again.
And look him in the face, y'know?
- Mm-mmm!
Hm?
Of course! She wants to go meet
her first love face-to-face
and see for herself
whether there are lingering feelings.
Wait! But that's not it!
Man! I gotta say I'm surprised.
I'd never expect this
from someone like Ryu.
He picked it 'cause it made him
think of Chizu.
So tell me.
Whenever you're alone with him...
...does your heart go "bwaa"?
I...
For the first time in my life,
whenever I see that boy,
my heart starts racing.
SQUEE!
Goodness, it sounds like
they're having fun.
Anyway, what about you two?
Did you get presents?
Yeah.
Uh-huh. Me too.
Oh wow, I love them.
They're so cute and totally you.
One hundred percent.
Good job, Kazehaya, you Sawako fanatic!
I think he's earned himself
a thank-you kiss!
- Huh?
- Did you?
- Did you?!
I can neither confirm nor deny.
- That's mean!
- Oh, c'mon!
I won't. And there's nothing you could say
or do to convince me otherwise.
- Then, how 'bout you?
- Huh?
What romantic gift did you get from Kento?
R-- roses.
Oh, enough about the rose!
I'm asking what you got!
I know! Kento got me roses.
A whole bouquet, in fact.
A bouquet!
Deep-red ones.
You... You're sure we're talking about
the same Kento,
the Japanese high-schooler?
Totally. Kento Miura.
Age sixteen, second year.
- Gotta see it!
- Sure. I took some pictures.
Whoa, you're right!
Those are red as hell!
Yep, and there's white
on the petals too.
That's so cute!
Yeah, but why are
the petals all scattered?
Because Joe
stepped on the bouquet.
Are-- are you serious? That jerk.
The instant I undid the wrapping,
it fell to pieces.
So I put them in a bowl.
Kento says that this rose
might stop existing in ten years.
Wait, why?
Well, apparently,
the florist told him that
the farmer who grows them is getting old.
Makes me wonder if a farmer
somewhere else is growing them.
I thought about that too.
Ten years from now...
I wonder what I'll be doing.
Ten years!
That's so far away,
I can't picture it, you know.
We'll be 27!
Maybe we'll all be married by then.
We might even have kids.
Ten years.
Ten years from now.
Ten whole years.
I sure hope we'll still be able
to spend time together.
What are you talking about?!
We'll be together forever!
Absolutely.
It's lunchtime, girls!
Yay, lunch!
Thank you so much!
Nothing fancy.
Just rice balls and soup.
- Thanks, Mom!
- Don't mention it.
For me, ten years ago
feels like yesterday.
I love seeing how excited you are.
Yano-chin went and got herself
a boyfriend, and he gave her fancy roses!
So did Chizu. He gave her this.
But he's not officially her boyfriend yet.
How absolutely gorgeous.
I haven't had this kind of girl talk
in so long.
I bet it's 'cause
Sawako doesn't like to share.
It's not like that at all!
Talking with Chizu and Ayane,
sharing pieces of our lives
with each other,
and even having lunch together...
It's such a perfect day.
Well, in that case, I think
they should stick around for dinner.
What?!
Yep! We're having
our Christmas party tonight.
Sawako even baked a cake for the occasion.
Wha-- She made a whole cake?
I'd love it if you tried some.
You sure that's okay?
Wait a sec.
Can we really intrude on a family thing?
Of course.
You know what they say.
The more, the merrier!
Here's an idea. Why don't you
ask Kazehaya to come over?
And why don't you two ladies
invite your boyfriends over too?
- Huh?!
- Oh, don't be shy.
- Go on!
- Good evening.
Oh dear. Welcome, boys. Come on in!
Thanks for having us.
You brought it with you?
And you showed it to them?
Uh... yeah.
There's a million reasons
why I wish you hadn't done that.
I... I'm sorry.
Is he mad?!
I'm pretty embarrassed about it too.
Gah!
GURGLE
I'm starving.
Th-- this way.
Make yourself at home, Kazehaya.
Oh, yeah, thanks.
Wait! Just a second!
It slammed shut!
Um, so,
did you really not have plans?
Yeah. I was free. It's fine.
And your family... doesn't mind?
No, they don't.
Um... did you have trouble getting here?
Nope, all good.
You don't have to worry.
Everything's fine.
Uh, uh...
Sorry, say that again?
- Um, well, you see, I, uh...
- Huh?
It happened only yesterday, so...
I thought I'd still be too shy
to say anything about it.
It's not what you think!
You were acting all sneaky,
so I kind of got curious.
I think you're acting way more sneaky
than both of them are.
It's hard to believe
that just yesterday,
we couldn't look each other in the eye.
Hi! Pardon the intrusion!
My yearning for Ayane
swept me to this place.
- Oh my! Welcome!
- Master!
Wow! Feels like forever
since we last talked.
Is it because we've slept since then?
Oh, I disagree.
Must be something wrong
with your perception of time.
Huh?
Honey, I'm--
- Welcome back!
- Wha--
- C'mon! Hurry, Dad!
Everything is ready!
It's good to see you again.
The whole gang is here tonight.
Oh.
This guy and I
have been friends since forever.
He's huge!
And I'm Ayane's boyfriend.
Slimy!
- Hm?
- Th... thank you for having us.
Last night, I'm sorry
we stayed out so late.
Are you sure
you're serious about dating her?
Yes.
Fine, then.
Hey, Dad!
Here, let me take your bag.
- Oh, right, here. It's strawberries.
- Ah, that's great!
- Hm?
- Thanks, Dad!
What the...
Sawako, you've grown.
Like, a whole heck of a lot.
Oh, have I?
I'm going to go prepare these.
Ahh.
- Oh, that hat!
- Huh?
Sawako was gonna give that to Kazehaya--
Mm-mm, mm-mm, mm-mm, mm-mm!
Mwah. Merry Christmas!
And a Happy New Year to you!
Honey, come to the living room
once you've changed!
Sure.
So what do you
wanna do on the 31st?
Ooh! New Year's Eve plans?
Oh, not just that!
It's Sawako's birthday too.
Wait, I had no idea you shared a birthday
with New Year's Eve.
We totally need to celebrate!
Aw!
Everybody's being so nice!
Right, so we're all meeting up
for New Year's Eve.
I think we should get together early.
- Wait, I forgot to mention.
- Hm?
If it'll be at midnight...
then I can't make it.
Last night, I got special permission
from my parents to stay out late,
so I was going to say thank you
with toshikoshi soba noodles this year.
Oh, is that a family favorite?
If it's Sawako,
I bet she cooks 'em herself.
None of that store-bought dashi
when she knows she could make her own.
- From scratch.
- Huh?
- Making soba...
- From scratch, you say?
This'll be my first time,
so I'm not sure they'll turn out too good.
Hm.
That's amazing!
Knowing you,
they'll come out perfect.
Thanks!
Yo, Papan!
What are you doing out here
all by your lonesome?
Why don't you come over here and join us?
Let me put this on you!
Ta-dah!
Argggggh!
We went ahead and decked the halls
something fierce while waiting for you.
Check it out!
Right, time to dig in, everyone.
- Cheers!
Hey, Papa.
Kazehaya's an incredibly nice guy,
isn't he, Sanada?
Ah, he's okay.
Last night, he listened to me
ramble on and on until the sun came up.
He did doze off a few times though,
which was super rude if you ask me.
Are you serious?!
If we could all
keep spending time together like this,
forever... how lovely would that be?
- Thanks for having us.
- Everything was delicious.
Sawa, I still gotta give you
your birthday gift, so I'll text you.
Uh... okay, thank you!
Me and Ayane are gonna head this way.
Oh.
Hey, uh... I gotta help my folks,
so I may not have a lot of time
between now and New Year's Eve.
But I can call you over winter break.
Yeah, me too! I might text you
just to say hello sometimes.
Cool.
Maybe... I'll call too.
Great. So will I.
Sir, I'm sorry that
we all dropped by today unannounced.
Thanks for your hospitality.
It's fine.
You're welcome to visit us anytime.
All of you.
As well as Kazehaya.
Thanks!
Dad.
You've been very understanding. Thank you.
For New Year's...
you should go out again this year.
You'll all be out past midnight, right?
You better bundle up!
I don't need you catchin' a cold!
Dad, hang on.
I'm doing it because I want to.
I thought it might be fun to do this...
that's why I chose it.
My soba...
...might not turn out very good this year,
but I'll give it my best shot!
Hey, honey.
Hmm?
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
SAWAKO-CHAN
Sawako looked
so happy today, didn't she?
Yes.
She did.
She's definitely one
to speak her mind, don't you think?
I'm glad.
It must mean she feels safe to do so.
Yeah. I think you're right.
She's much more mature than I realized.
To tell you the truth,
it just took me by surprise.
Ten years, huh?
Will it feel like forever?
Or pass in the blink of an eye?
If you think about it,
once graduation rolls around
and she decides to move away for school...
that leaves us all
with one more year of living together.
I'm happy.
So, so happy... to get to spend time
with the people I love most in the world!
I wish it could go on... forever.
Just like this.